<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to the Liberty Ward on The Liberty Ward News and Events</title>
    <link>https://libertyward.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to the Liberty Ward on The Liberty Ward News and Events</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 10:39:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://libertyward.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Reliance Devotional</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/self_reliance_feb2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 10:39:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/self_reliance_feb2019/</guid>
      <description>Members (and friends) can choose from five different groups: Personal Finances, Starting and Growing My Business, Find a Better Job, Education for Better Work, and Emergency Preparedness.
Contact Nick and Norma King for information: 816-679-1599 or 816-550-5556. Nursery will be provided.
Where: Liberty Stake center
When: February 17th at 6:00pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stake Missionary Prep Class</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/missionaryprep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/missionaryprep/</guid>
      <description>New Age Range Invited! All Mia Maids, Teacher, Laurels, and Priests are invited to attend. Refreshments Served
Where: Liberty Stake Center RS Room
When: January 13th 7:30-8:30 am</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elders Quorum Presidency Training</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/eq_training_jan2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 10:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/eq_training_jan2019/</guid>
      <description>For all Elders Quorum Presidency members and secretaries.
Where: Liberty Stake Center - Relief Society Room
When: January 27th at 6:00am</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interfaith Youth Dance</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/youth_dance_jan2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 10:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/youth_dance_jan2019/</guid>
      <description>Interfaith Youth Dance
Where: Liberty Stake Center
When: January 19th, 8:00-11:00pm
Be there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ward Conference Schedule</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/ward-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/ward-conference/</guid>
      <description>The annual conference of the Liberty Ward will be held January 13, 2019 As described in the Handbook, the purposes of these conferences are to “strengthen faith and testimony, provide gospel instruction, conduct business, and evaluate activity.” Our Stake Vision is: ​“​Every Member of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints in the Liberty Stake is Consecrated Unto the Lord​”. ​The schedule and assignments will be as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Singles Activities</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/midsinglesjan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/midsinglesjan/</guid>
      <description> Sunday, Jan 6 - Pot Luck at Zach&amp;rsquo;s House, 4 pm (1104 Canterbury Lane, Liberty) Monday, Jan 7 - FHE Thursday, Jan 10 - MSA Religion Class, Liberty Stake Center Saturday, Jan 12 - 4 pm temple session. Eating out to follow, usually between 6:30-7:00 pm  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stake Family History Centers</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/fhc-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/fhc-change/</guid>
      <description>Per direction from Salt Lake, Temple and Family History Consultants meet with individuals on a one-on-one basis&amp;ndash;preferably in the home. Liberty Stake Family History Centers will now be open for use By Approintment Only.
Please contact the Stake Lead Temple and Family History Consultant, Dianna Jensen, to schedule time in the Family History Center:
Dianna Jensen 925-699-0401 diannajensen07@gmail.com
Members are also encouraged to contact their ward consultants for Family History assistance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Year Old Camp Canceled for 2019</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/post/11-year-old-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/post/11-year-old-camp/</guid>
      <description>Multi-stake 11 year old Scout Camp has been cancelled for 2019 due to the changes in the age to join Young Men&amp;rsquo;s. Instead 11 year old boys are encouraged to join their LDS troop attending Scout Camp next summer. The Church has modified camping guidelines as follows:
With parents&amp;rsquo; approval, Deacons may now attend camps before their 12th birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Our Ward</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/about-ward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/about-ward/</guid>
      <description>Bishopric  Auxiliary Presidents and Ward Leaders  Full Time Missionaries Elder Spencer Goff Portugal Lisbon Mission sgoff@myldsmail.net</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liberty Ward Vision</title>
      <link>https://libertyward.org/ward-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libertyward.org/ward-vision/</guid>
      <description>from Bishop Wheeler, January 5, 2019
On January 13th we will hold our annual ward conference. This is a great opportunity to hear and learn from our stake leaders. The ward conference will be held during our normal church time 9:00-11:00 am at the Clayview Building. I encourage all of you to attend.
Prior to the conference, I would encourage each of you to take some time to ponder, discuss, and determine what your family goals and plan will be to help the work of salvation in this year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>